Hey! Come on, come on!
Watch out!
Let's go!
Watch your back, attack is on the way
So feel around with the cards you play.
Lookin' out, suspiscion, for they keep deceivin'
Aim for every minute that you believe is right
Sillhouette, conspiracies indefinite
Never fool, gotta stay cool. Smoke another cigarette
Whatever you believin' now conflicts
Observin' as the middle-man
pazuru wa torturing with their aizu
パズルはtorturing with their 合図
(With your eyes!)
aragaenai ubaiai
抗えない奪い合い
utagae yo, shinsou wo
疑えよ、真相を
hirugaesu Every night
翻す Every night
(Every night, now!)
Standing inside the squall
me no mae no subete ga Suggestion
目の前の全てが Suggestion
(Tell me what it says!)
"Anytime, you'll find what you should know!"
Here we go now!
Let's go! Come on, come on! On a journey!
mitsuketa Illusion
見つけたIllusion
hakanai sutoorii tsunagaru Season he
儚いストーリー繋がるSeasonへ
Come on! nee, come on! On a journey!
Come on ! ねぇ, come on! On a journey!
sagashiteru kagi wo
探してる鍵を
(Where's the key?)
Just move and you'll find out
Let's go! Come on, come on! On a journey!
nee, shiritai deshou?
ねぇ、知りたいでしょう？
egaku basho ni tadoritsuku made
描く場所に辿り着くまで
Come on! nee, come on! On a journey!
Come on ! ねぇ, come on! On a journey!
unmei ga yobiyoseta michibiki wa akashi
運命が呼び寄せた導きは証
Stay cool! It's never really what it seems.
(You gotta use your eyes to perceive the wind)